https://www.workerscompensation.com/privacy_policy.php

I Need Workers' Comp Insurance
I'm Injured What Do I Do?
WorkersCompensation.com COVID-19 Statement & Actions
I Need Workers' Comp Insurance
I'm Injured What Do I Do?
WorkersCompensation.com Privacy Policy and Disclaimer
Home
WorkersCompensation.com Privacy Policy
The Statement describes our Privacy Policy and Disclaimer regarding
WorkersCompensation.com information located on this website. WorkersCompensation.com
recognizes the importance of keeping your personal information
private in the online environment. It is our policy that any personal information
provided by a user will never be shared with any third party or any person or
organization not directly involved in WorkersCompensation.com related transactions.
Information for the WorkersCompensation.com website is gathered in two methods:
First Method:
Information for the website is gathered through tracking of general online website statistics; for example,
how many visitors to the site, which pages were viewed, what files accessed, etc.
While certain features of the site may employ "cookies" to better
facilitate services, at no time is any personal or specific information about the
visitor collected without specific knowledge or awareness of the visitor knowingly
providing it.
Second Method:
Information for the website is gathered through direct interaction with the specific visitor to
the site; for example, completion and direct submission of an online form, email from the visitor
to WorkersCompensation.com, etc.
Limit of Liability/Disclaimer of Warranty
This
website contains general information about legal matters.  The information
is not advice or legal counsel, and should not be treated as such.  If you
have any specific questions about any legal matter you should consult your
attorney or other professional legal services provider as soon as
possible.  You should never delay seeking legal advice, disregard legal
advice, or commence or discontinue any legal action because of information on
this website. Your use of this site constitues an acceptance of the terms of this site.
WorkersCompensation.com makes no representations or
warranties with respect to the accuracy and completeness of the contents of
this site and specifically disclaim any implied warranties of merchantability
or fitness for a particular purpose. There are no warranties extended beyond
the descriptions contained in this paragraph. It should be realized that laws
change daily and the viewer should not rely on this site for specific legal
information, and should consult an attorney for guidance and directions in
interpreting laws, statues and regulations. No warranty may be created or
extended by sales representatives or written sales materials. The accuracy and
completeness provided herein and any opinions stated herein are not guaranteed
or warranted to produce any particular results.
The use of the word "the best" in this site should not be construed to indicate that the
publishers presume to pass upon the qualifications or the merits of the persons
listed herein. Rather, it indicates that all of the listees arethe best to
do business in their particular field and have requested to be listed by
WorkersCompensation.com. Our Professional Directory listings are open, and we
do not permit exclusive or limited representation.
The
WorkersCompensation.com site is the result of suggestions made by persons
involved in all aspects of the Workers Compensation Industry to provide a
national, state and local reference source for everyone.
The staff of
WorkersCompensation.com earnestly strives to provide the visitor with important
and pertinent data necessary to help in their search for Workers' Compensation
information. We also will endeavor to serve the industry as the authoritative
source of competent and qualified professionals for your particular need. To
help maintain these standards, we earnestly solicit your comments and
suggestions. Please email info@workerscompensation.com
WorkersCompensation.com, LLC. | All Rights Reserved About Us | Advertise with Us | Contact Us | WorkCompResearch.com | Privacy Policy | Terms | Advertiser Login
